Rules

To do this, you must find each (x1,y1) coordinates containing a node, and display the (x2,y2) coordinates of the next node to the right, and the (x3,y3) coordinates of the next node to the bottom within the grid.

If a neighbor does not exist, you must output the coordinates -1 -1 instead of (x2,y2) and/or (x3,y3).

You lose if:
You give an incorrect neighbor for a node.
You give the neighbors for an empty cell.
You compute the same node twice.
You forget to compute the neighbors of a node.
 
Victory Conditions
You win when all nodes have been correctly displayed.

Game Input

The program must first read the initialization data from standard input. Then, provide to the standard output one line per instruction.

Initialization input
Line 1: one integer width for the number of cells along the x axis.
Line 2: one integer height for the number of cells along the y axis.
Next height lines: A string  line  containing  width  characters. A dot . represents an empty cell. A zero 0 represents a cell containing a node.
Output for one game turn
One line per node. Six integers on each line:   x1  y1  x2  y2  x3  y3

Where:
(x1,y1) the coordinates of a node
(x2,y2) the coordinates of the closest neighbor on the right of the node
(x3,y3) the coordinates of the closest bottom neighbor
If there is no neighbor, the coordinates should be -1 -1.

Constraints
0 < width ≤ 30
0 < height ≤ 30
0 ≤ x1 < width
0 ≤ y1 < height
-1 ≤ x2, x3 < width
-1 ≤ y2, y3 < height
Alloted response time to first output line ≤ 1s.
Response time between two output lines ≤ 100ms